<resources>
    <string name="app_name">KotlinExamples</string>
    <string name="app_bar_about">Android is a mobile operating system developed by Google, based on the Linux kernel and designed primarily for touchscreen mobile devices such as smartphones and tablets. Android\'s user interface is mainly based on direct manipulation, using touch gestures that loosely correspond to real-world actions, such as swiping, tapping and pinching, to manipulate on-screen objects, along with a virtual keyboard for text input. In addition to touchscreen devices, Google has further developed Android TV for televisions, Android Auto for cars, and Android Wear for wrist watches, each with a specialized user interface. Variants of Android are also used on game consoles, digital cameras, PCs and other electronics.</string>
    <string name="app_bar_about_me">Google Inc. is an American multinational technology company that specializes in Internet-related services and products. These include online advertising technologies, search, cloud computing, software, and hardware. Google was founded in 1998 by Larry Page and Sergey Brin while they were Ph.D. students at Stanford University, in California.</string>
    <string name="app_bar_kotlin">Kotlin is a statically-typed programming language that runs on the Java virtual machine and also can be compiled to JavaScript source code or uses the LLVM compiler infrastructure. Its primary development is from a team of JetBrains programmers based in Saint Petersburg, Russia.[2] While the syntax is not compatible with Java, Kotlin is designed to interoperate with Java code and is reliant on Java code from the existing Java Class Library, such as the collections framework.</string>
    <string name="share_text">Share my idea</string>
    <string name="default_notification_channel_id" translatable="false">fcm_default_channel</string>
    <string name="default_notification_channel_name" translatable="true">News</string>
    <string name="quickstart_message">Click the SUBSCRIBE TO NEWS button below to subscribe to the
        news topic. Messages sent to the news topic will be received. The LOG TOKEN button logs the
        InstanceID token to logcat.</string>
    <string name="subscribe_to_news">Subscribe To News</string>
    <string name="log_token">Log Token</string>

    <string name="msg_subscribed">Subscribed to news topic</string>
    <string name="msg_token_fmt" translatable="false">InstanceID Token: %s</string>

    <string name="first_example">First Example</string>
    <string name="second_example">Second Example</string>
    <string name="pdf_with_index" >PdfRendererBasic (%1$d/%2$d)</string>
    <string name="intro_message">
        <![CDATA[
            This sample demonstrates how to use PdfRenderer to display PDF documents on the screen.
        ]]>
    </string>
</resources>
